CHARITY SUN

UX/UI DESIGNER

Location

San Diego, California

Email

charitydesignx@gmail.com

Portfolio

 $\frac{\texttt{charitysun.myportfoli}}{\texttt{o.com}}$

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/charitysun

SKILLS

State and National Tobacco Datasets

Google Analytics

Data Analysis

Project management

Presentation and Communication

Qualtrics

Tableau

Figma

User Research

IA Principles

User Personas

Journey Maps

Wireframing

Prototyping

User Flows

HTML and CSS Fundamentals

JavaScript Basics

Responsive CSS Layout

EDUCATION

CERTIFICATE IN UX DESIGN

CareerFoundry August 2023 - April 2024

Frontend Development for Designers

CareerFoundry March 2024 - April 2024

Google Analytics Certificate Skillshop - 2024

PROFILE

Creative UX designer who combines problem-solving and aesthetics to create effective solutions. Versed in UX methodologies such as research, analyzing data, uncovering pain points, ideating, prototyping, and communicating solutions. Versed in state and national tobacco datasets, project management and market research.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ASSISTANT RESEARCHER / UX INTERN

UC San Diego Kick It California | Sep 2023 - Present

- Familiarized myself with tobacco surveys and various datasets to effectively answer business goals and questions.
- Analyzed state and national datasets such as Ask CHIS, U.S. Census, CDC, BRFSS, NHIS, SAMHSA, NSDUH, and PATH to research and find supporting data for Asian Smokers' Quitline (ASQ) projects
- Utilized **research and data skills** to direct ASQ projects in a way that met business goals and objectives.
- Conducted **market research** to see if Asian Smokers' Quitline (ASQ) should still exists and gave a rough estimate of ASQ's current market share.
- Helped guide and champion **UX principles and methods** as the first UX researcher in the organization.
- Showed competence in efficient developer hand-off and communication.

PUBLISHED THREE CASE STUDIES

UX design course at CareerFoundry | Aug 2023 - Sep 2023

- Challenge: The challenge was to research, develop, design, and publish three case studies documenting my UX skills and thought process.
- **Process**: I **collaborated** with fellow designers and course mentors to complete my three projects and document my process in multiple case studies. **Research** was used to guide and inform my projects.
- **Solution**: Three detailed case studies showing my thought process and UX skills were published on my portfolio website and announced in a post on my LinkedIn. All case studies showcase a **good balance between text, visuals**, and presentation. **Adobe** portfolio was used to **publish my works online**.

GAME GRAPHICS DESIGNER

Toonidy Project | May 2022 - June 2022

- Collaborated with my client to understand project objectives and develop **visual solutions**
- Creatively designed visually pleasing paper airplane graphics to my clients satisfaction
- Ensured the accuracy of all artwork and file format before handoff

BRAND AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Kodiak Project | Jan 2020 - Feb 2020

- Challenge: Clients was looking for designed and printed materials for her rental house.
- **Process**: I collaborated and communicated with my client to accurately **design signs and direction cards** to her expectations. Drafts and ideas were created and shown to my client.
- Solution: Final designs were finalized, printed, and handed off to my client.